Register to The Kay Swift Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Music, 1911-1986; Series I; 4.6' (11 boxes)
  - Instrumental Works, I.C
    - [Theme and variations] Theme and variations for H.G. / Kay Swift., 1 manuscript part (6 p.); 32 cm. (Box 9, Folder 302)
      Lacks 4th variation.
    - [Theme and variations], 1 manuscript part (6 p.); 32 cm. (Box 9, Folder 303)
      Holograph in ink, annotations in pencil, blue ink, and taped on.
      Contents: Variation 2 (2 p.). Variation 3 (2 p.). Variation 4 (2 p.)
    - [Theme and variations] Variation 4., 1 manuscript score (8 p.); 32 cm. (Box 9, Folder 304)
    - [Trick or treat], 1 manuscript condensed score (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 9, Folder 305)
    - [Tuesday Blues (Sketches)], 2 p. of music; 32 cm. (Box 9, Folder 306)
      Dated: March 20.
    - [Two of us here] Two of us here / Kay Swift., 1 manuscript p. of music; 32 cm. (Box 9, Folder 307)
      Holograph (?) in pencil, on transparencies.
    - [Two of us here] Gigue., 1 manuscript p. of music; 32 cm. (Box 9, Folder 307)
      Note at top: Printed, with title "Two of Us Here."
    - [Unidentified composition], 1 manuscript score (2 p.); 41 cm. (Box 10, Folder 308)
      Pagination assigns 2 consecutive numbers to each p.
      For flute, clarinet, trumpet I, trumpet II, trombone, accordion, percussion, and double bass.
    - [Unidentified composition], 16 manuscript p. of music; 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 308)
      Lacks all before p. 8.
    - [Unidentified composition], 2 manuscript p. of music; 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 308)
    - [Unidentified composition], 1 manuscript condensed score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 308)
      Dated: Mar. 19,'61 (?)
    - [Unidentified composition], 3 manuscript p. of music; 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 308)
      Note on cover: Incomplete copy of piano piece from book dedicated to Kathy + Rachel.
      Kathy [Katharine Weber] and Rachel [Levine] are two of Kay Swift's granddaughters.
    - [Unidentified composition], 1 manuscript piano score (14 p.); 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 309)
      Holograph in ink, annotations in pencil, blue and red ink, and pasted in.
      Incomplete, lacks all before p. 11.
    - [Unidentified composition], 4 manuscript p. of music; 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 309)
      On p. 1: Tempo di Mazurka.
      Dated: July 8th 1926.
    - [Unidentified composition], 1 manuscript p. of music; 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 309)
    - [Unidentified composition], 1 manuscript score (8 p.); 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 310)
      Incomplete, lacks p. 1-4 and all after p. 8.
      For flute I, flute II, violin, viola, and violoncello.
    - [Unidentified composition], 1 manuscript score (4 p.); 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 310)
      Copyist's manuscript in pencil.
      For flute, clarinet, trumpet, piano, violin I, violin II, viola, violoncello, double bass, and percussion.
    - [Unidentified composition], 5 manuscript p. of music; 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 310)
      Music crossed out at top of page 1 and on verso of 5.
    - [Unidentified composition (Sketches)], 4 leaves of music; 34 cm. (Box 10, Folder 310)
      Note in ink at top of 1 p.: original pantomime for Comedy Club-circa '1928-.
    - [Unidentified composition (Sketches)], 8 leaves of music; 34 cm. (Box 10, Folder 311)
      Probably for stage work.
      Some sections labeled according to stage action.
      At top of page 1: HEAVEN.
    - [Unidentified composition (Sketches)], 9 leaves of music; various sizes. (Box 10, Folder 312)
      3 sets of sketches for trombone and orchestra composition.
      1 page dated: 4/12/72.
      1 page dated: 2/6/'76.
      1 page dated: 2/8/1978.
    - [Unidentified composition (Sketches)], 4 leaves of music; 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 313)
      For trombone and orchestra.
      Dated: 26/6/1974.
    - [Waltz], 2 manuscript p. of music; 31 cm. (Box 10, Folder 314)
      Incomplete, lacks p. 1-3 and all after p. 5.
    - [Whistling in the dark (Sketches)] Whistling in the dark., 1 manuscript p. of music; 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 315)
      At top: (old title-1928 and tune, or 1929).
      Dated: October '72.
    - [Yes, I shall] Yes, I shall / Kay Swift, 1 manuscript piano score (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 316)
      At top of page 1: Begun 7/8/72 (began it).
    - [Yes, I shall (Sketches)], 3 leaves of music; 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 317)
      At top of 1 p.: old copy Yes, I Shall [dated: 7/8/72 Revised 9/11/72].
      At top of 1 p.: 2nd theme for "Yes, I Shall."
  - Unidentified Sketches, I.D
    - [Sketches], 100 p.; 32 cm. (Box 11, Folder 361)
      In Passantino spiral music blank book.
      Some labeled and dated.
    - [Sketches] Kay Swift: Tunes., 41 p.; 34 cm. (Box 11, Folder 362)
      Bound music sketch book.
    - [Sketches], 37 leaves of music; 35 cm. (Box 11, Folder 363)
    - [Song sketches], 15 leaves of music; various sizes. (Box 11, Folder 364)
      Dated.
    - [Song sketches], 42 leaves of music; various sizes. (Box 11, Folder 365)
      Not dated.
    - [Instrumental sketches], 103 leaves of music; various sizes. (Box 11, Folder 366)
    - [Instrumental sketches], 107 leaves of music; various sizes. (Box 11, Folder 367)
    - [Unidentified sketches], 67 leaves of music; various sizes. (Box 11, Folder 368)
    - [Unidentified sketches], 47 leaves of music; various sizes. (Box 11, Folder 369)
  - Music by Other Composers Arranged by Kay Swift, I.E
    - [My heart ever faithful, arr.], Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; 9 manuscript parts; 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 318)
      Copyist's manuscript in ink, annotations in red and blue pencil, and ink.
      Arr. for: flute I, flute II, violin, viola, and violoncello.
      Part for violoncello (IA) is torn.
    - [Bourrée, arr.], Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750; 5 manuscript parts; various sizes. (Box 10, Folder 319)
      Manuscript in Kay Swift's hand in ink, annotations in pencil.
      3 parts for flute, 1 for trombone, 2 for flute and trombone
      Based on the bourrée movement from the Cello Suite in C major (BWV1009)
      For wedding of Kay Swift's granddaughter Katharine Swift Kaufman and Nicholas Weber on September 19, 1976.
    - [Roar of the greasepaint, the smell of the crowd. Feeling good, arr.] Feeling good / Leslie Bricusse; Anthony Newley; Kay Swift., Bricusse, Leslie; 1 manuscript chorus score (6 p.); 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 320)
      Manuscript in Kay Swift's hand in ink, annotations in blue ink.
    - [Roar of the greasepaint, the smell of the crowd. Feeling good, arr. (Sketches)], Bricusse, Leslie; 3 p. of music; various sizes. (Box 10, Folder 321)
    - [Roar of the greasepaint, the smell of the crowd. Joker, arr. (Sketches)], Bricusse, Leslie; 3 p. of music; 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 322)
      Manuscript in Kay Swift's hand in pencil and ink.
      Sketches are for choral arrangement.
      At bottom of 1 p.: Intro., Winning Song.
    - [Let 'em eat cake. Comes the revolution, arr.] Comes the revolution / music by George Gershwin; lyrics by Ira Gershwin; piano arr. Kay Swift., Gershwin, George, 1898-1937; 1 manuscript vocal score (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 323)
    - [Yankee Doodle blues] Yankee Doodle blues / words by Irving Caesar and B.G. De Sylva; music by George Gershwin -- New York: New World Music, 1922., Gershwin, George, 1898-1937; 1 vocal score (5 p.); 31 cm. (Box 10, Folder 324)
      Photocopy, annotated by Kay Swift in pencil and red pencil.
    - [Yankee Doodle blues, arr.] Yankee Doodle blues / music by George Gershwin; lyric by B.G. De Silva [sic] + Irving Caesar; arr. Kay Swift., Gershwin, George, 1898-1937; 1 manuscript score (14 p.) + 1 manuscript part; 36 cm. (Box 10, Folder 325)
      Manuscript in Kay Swift's hand in pencil, on transparencies, annotations in ink.
      Arr. for: chorus (SATB), trumpet (cornet), percussion, and piano
      2 copies (1 bound photocopy)
      Part for trumpet (3 p.)
    - [Yankee Doodle blues, arr.] Yankee Doodle blues / George Gershwin; arr. Kay Swift., Gershwin, George, 1898-1937; 1 manuscript chorus score (9 p.); 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 326)
      Includes piano accompaniment and instrumental cues.
      Incomplete, lacks p. 2-5 and all after p. 9.
    - [Yankee Doodle blues, arr. (Sketches)], Gershwin, George, 1898-1937; 5 leaves of music; 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 327)
      At top of 1 p.: For Eva [Jessye]
    - [Orfeo. Selections, arr.], Gluck, Christoph Willibald, Ritter von, 1714-1787; 8 manuscript parts; 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 328)
      Copyist's manuscript in ink, annotations in pencil, and red and blue pencil.
    - [Hair. Aquarius, arr.] Aquarius / music by Gail [sic] MacDermott; lyric by James Rado [and] George Ragni; arr. Kay Swift., MacDermott, Galt; 1 manuscript chorus score (8 p.); 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 329)
      Manuscript in Kay Swift's hand in pencil, annotations in red pencil and ink.
      Found in envelope marked: "Aquarius" arranged for 5 voices + piano (orchestration planned) by Kay Swift.
    - [Hair. Aquarius, arr.], MacDermott, Galt; 1 manuscript chorus score (8 p.); 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 330)
      At top of all p.: Old Copy.
    - [Hair. Aquarius, arr. (Sketches)], MacDermott, Galt; 2 leaves of music; 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 331)
      Dated: 1/6/71.
  - Music by Other Composers, I.F
    - [Winners circle. Saggy and Joppy (Sketches)], Beaudry, Ralph; 1 leaf; 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 332)
      Note at bottom: Suggested shorter intro.-thought you might like-since this is a humorous, "Ira-type" song- but no sads here if no like.
      See letter from Don Rose to Katharine Weber dated July 25, 1993.
    - [Crazy cantata] Crazy cantata (Three blind mice) / by Robert Russell Bennett - New York: Chappell, 1947., Bennett, Robert Russell, 1894-1981; 1 chorus score (20 p.); 26 cm. (Box 10, Folder 333)
      Inscription on title page: Love to Kay from Rus.
    - [There she goes] There she goes., Bennett, Robert Russell, 1894-1981; 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); various sizes. (Box 10, Folder 334)
      Page 3 cut in half.
      New lyric by Kay Swift entitled "There He Goes" [title from 1st line] and letter from Robert Russell Bennett dated October 26, 1957 laid in.
    - [Erev voker] Erev voker / by Leon Berger., Berger, Leon; 1 manuscript chorus score (2 p.); 29 cm. (Box 10, Folder 335)
      Part for cantor solo and SATB chorus.
      Kay Swift probably met Leon Berger at the Light House (an institution for the blind in New York City)
    - [A little bit independent] A little bit independent / words by Edgar Leslie; music by Joe Burke -- New York: Donaldson, Douglas & Gumble, 1935., Burke, Joe; 1 vocal score (5 p.); 31 cm. (Box 7, Folder 186)
      Found with photostat of "I'd Walk a Mile for You" and letter in folder marked: Photostat of "I'd Walk A Mile For You" by K.S. + Al Stillman plus letter to people who stole (consciously or not) the song + published it.
    - [Sweet content] Sweet content., 1 manuscript part (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 336)
      Creator unknown, possibly Thomas Dekker.
    - [Why haven't fishes got feet?] Why haven't fishes got feet? / music and lyrics by April., Gagliano, April; 1 manuscript vocal score (6 p.); 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 337)
      Manuscript in Kay Swift's hand in ink.
      April [Gagliano] is one of Kay Swift and James Warburg's three daughters.
    - [Why haven't fishes got feet?] Why haven't fishes / by April., Gagliano, April; 1 manuscript vocal score (7 p.); 28 cm. (Box 10, Folder 337)
    - [Let 'em eat cake], Gershwin, George, 1898-1937; 1 manuscript vocal score (2 versions); 23 cm. (Box 27, Folder 734-724)
      Photocopy from microfilm.
      Manuscript in Library of Congress.
      Kay Swift helped to reconstruct score.
      Bound in 2 black spiral notebooks.
    - [Let 'em eat cake. First lady and first gentleman (Sketches)], Gershwin, George, 1898-1937; 6 leaves of music; various sizes. (Box 10, Folder 338)
    - [Let 'em eat cake. Union league], Gershwin, George, 1898-1937; 1 manuscript vocal score (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 339)
    - [Let 'em eat cake. Union league] Union league / lyric-Ira Gershwin; music-George Gershwin; realization by-Kay Swift., Gershwin, George, 1898-1937; 1 manuscript vocal score (7 p.); 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 339)
      Manuscript in Kay Swift's hand in pencil and blue ink, and Don Rose's hand in black ink.
      Verso of p. 7 contains pencil sketch in Kay Swift's hand for first ending.
    - [Rhapsodies, piano, orchestra, no. 2], Gershwin, George, 1898-1937; 1 manuscript score ([45] p.); 26 cm. (Box 10, Folder 340)
      Arr. for: 2 pianos.
      Found in folder marked: 2nd Rhapsody, photostat - missing 20 pages - 7/29 [?]/'72.
      1st page of unidentified score in same hand laid in.
    - [Rhapsodies, piano, orchestra, no. 2] 2nd rhapsody for piano and orchestra / George Gershwin., Gershwin, George, 1898-1937; 1 score (44 p.); 34 cm. (Box 10, Folder 341)
      Negative proof sheets.
      At top of all p.: 1st proof.
      Found in envelope marked: 2nd Rhapsody photostat, score- + other mus. + notes on material (G.G.) needed for DR recording.
    - [Selections (Sketches)], Gershwin, George, 1898-1937; 2 leaves of music; 36 cm. (Box 10, Folder 342)
      Contents: Harlem serenade. Sleepless night. Southern tune. Sleepless night (refrain)
      At bottom of 1 p.: George Gershwin Tunebook.
      1 page dated: 1925-26.
      1 page dated: 1933-37.
    - [Selections (Sketches)], Gershwin, George, 1898-1937; 5 leaves; 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 343)
      From George Gershwin manuscript once belonging to Kay Swift now at the Library of Congress.
      Photographs of these and additional p. in folder "George Gershwin Scrapbook." (20/580)
    - [Shocking Miss Pilgrim. Changing my tune] Changing my tune / George Gershwin; Ira Gershwin., Gershwin, George, 1898-1937; 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 344)
      Manuscript in Kay Swift's hand in ink, annotations in ink.
    - [Shocking Miss Pilgrim. Changing my tune] Changing my tune / words by Ira Gershwin; music by George Gershwin -- New York: Gershwin Publishing Corporation, 1946., Gershwin, George, 1898-1937; 1 vocal score (5 p.); 28 cm. (Box 10, Folder 344)
      Reconstruction by Kay Swift and Ira Gershwin from George Gershwin sketches for the 20th-Century Fox film.
    - [Shocking Miss Pilgrim. Tour of the town] Tour of the town / lyric by Ira Gershwin A.S.C.A.P.; music by George Gershwin A.S.C.A.P.; piano arr. Kay Swift., Gershwin, George, 1898-1937; 1 manuscript vocal score (13 p.); 28 cm. (Box 10, Folder 344)
      At top of page 1: O.K. Ira Gershwin [signed] O.K. Kay Swift [signed]
      Dated: Sept 27'45.
    - [Sleepless night] Prelude: Gershwin melody #17 (Sleepless night), Gershwin, George, 1898-1937; 4 p. of music; 36 cm. (Box 10, Folder 345)
      Manuscript in Kay Swift's hand (photocopy, last page is holograph)
      At bottom of p. 4: "Sleepless Night" fragment.
      Dated: 1925/26.
    - [Songs. Selections], Gershwin, George, 1898-1937; 17 vocal scores; various sizes. (Box 10, Folder 346)
      Individual song publications, some photocopy.
      Contents: (I've got) Beginner's luck. By Strauss. Hi-ho! I love to rhyme. Innocent ingenue baby (2 copies [1 photocopy], both incomplete). Isn't it a pity. I've got a crush on you. I've got to be there. Kickin' the clouds away. Let's call the whole thing off. Luckiest man in the world. My cousin in Milwaukee. Slap that bass. So what? That lost barber shop chord. They all laughed. They can't take that away from me.
    - [Songs. Selections] George Gershwin song album -- New York: Harms, 1938., Gershwin, George, 1898-1937; 1 vocal score (48 p.); 31 cm. (Box 10, Folder 347)
      Contents: The man I love. Someone to watch over me. Fascinating rhythm. Clap yo' hands. Oh, lady be good. Sweet and low-down. Fidgety feet. That certain feeling. Do-do-do. So am I. When do we dance?
    - [Strike up the band. Overture, arr.] Strike up the band - overture / [music] George Gershwin; arr. by Don Rose., Gershwin, George, 1898-1937; 1 manuscript condensed score (22 p.); 36 cm. (Box 11, Folder 348)
      Copyist's manuscript in ink, on transparencies, annotations in blue pencil.
    - [Waltzes, piano] Two waltzes in C / by George Gershwin; edited by Ira Gershwin; adapted by Saul Chaplin -- [S.l.]: New World, 1971., Gershwin, George, 1898-1937; 7 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 11, Folder 349)
      Printed on inside of cover: From a musical sequence written for, but not used in, PARDON MY ENGLISH, 1933.
    - [Waltzes, piano, no. 1], Gershwin, George, 1898-1937; 2 manuscript p. of music; 35 cm. (Box 11, Folder 349)
      From Two Waltzes in C.
      At top: To Angel (?) gg [George Gershwin]
    - [Unidentified song], Henley, W.E.; 1 manuscript vocal score (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 11, Folder 350)
      Manuscript in Kay Swift's hand (?) in pencil.
      First line: A wink from...falling across a wintry sky.
      Unidentified sketches on 2nd leaf.
    - Victor Herbert Waltz., Herbert, Victor, 1859-1924; 1 manuscript piano score (5 p.); 18 cm. (Box 11, Folder 351)
    - [March down to Jerdon] March down to Jerdon / edited and arr. by Eva A. Jessye -- New York: Robbins-Engel, 1927., Jessye, Eva A.; 1 vocal score (2 p.); 28 cm. (Box 11, Folder 352)
      At top of page 1: * Am ... Spiritual ... adaption.
      Signed under title: Eva Jessye.
      Eva Jessye was choral director for the original production of Porgy and Bess.
    - [Empire state] Empire state / "Clarence Butler.", Johnstone, Arthur Edward; 1 manuscript vocal score (6 p.); 35 cm. (Box 11, Folder 353)
      Copyist's manuscript in ink, text typed in blue, annotations in red ink.
      Johnstone, one of Kay Swift's composition teachers, occasionally used the pseudonym Clarence Butler.
      Note laid in.
    - [Katharine] Katharine / Arthur Edward Johnstone., Johnstone, Arthur Edward; 1 mamuscript page of music; 34 cm. (Box 11, Folder 354)
      Copyist's manuscript in ink, annotations in red ink.
      Dedicated to Kay Swift.
    - [Oh, will yez hear the tale o' Peggy and Me!] Oh, will yez hear the tale o' Peggy and me! / [music] Arthur Edward Johnstone., Johnstone, Arthur Edward; 7 manuscript p. of music; 35 cm. (Box 11, Folder 355)
    - [Where have I seen your face before] Where have I seen your face before / lyric by: Yip Harburg; music by: Burton Lane., Lane, Burton, 1912-1997; 1 manuscript vocal score (6 p.); 28 cm. (Box 11, Folder 356)
      At bottom of page 1: Copyright (c) 1981 by Chappell & Co., Inc.
    - [Carnival marche, arr.], Levant, Oscar, 1906-1972; Carnival marche / comp. Oscar Levant; arr. by Charles Maxwell. (Box 11, Folder 357)
      1 manuscript piano score (4 p.); 36 cm.
    - [Not so very long ago] Not so very long ago / Oscar Levant., Levant, Oscar, 1906-1972; 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 11, Folder 357)
    - [Re ci chiama: Carnival-king and country cali...] Il re ci chiama: Carnival-king and country cali... / lyric by William Kernell; music by Oscar Levant., Levant, Oscar, 1906-1972; 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 36 cm. (Box 11, Folder 357)
      At top of page 1: FILM-CHARLIE CHAN AT THE OPERA.
    - [Young in Heart], Levant, Oscar, 1906-1972; 1 manuscript piano score (1 p.); 36 cm. (Box 11, Folder 357)
      At bottom: Young In Heart Music by Oscar Levant Lyrics by Stanley Adams
    - [Angels] Angels / J. McClusky., McClusky, J.; 1 manuscript piano score (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 11, Folder 358)
      At top: Fine + Dandy.
    - [Pablo's circus], Stires, Ernest; Pablo's circus: One act opera for children of all ages / music by Ernest Stires; libretto by Benjamin Dunlap. (Box 27, Folder 725)
      1 manuscript vocal score (94 p.); 28 cm.
    - Libretto for same., 69 p.; 28 cm. (Box 27, Folder 725)
      Typescript (photocopy)
    - [Hidden] Hidden / words by S.F. Livingston; music by Gertrude H. Swift., Swift, Gertrude Horton Dorr; 1 manuscript vocal score (2 p.); 35 cm. (Box 11, Folder 359)
      Found in envelope marked: Wurteser[?] song by Gertrude Swift, composed by her music-in August, 1894.
      Gertrude H[orton Dorr] Swift is Kay Swift's grandmother.
      Dated: August 1894.
    - [Nigun bialik] Nigun bialik., Unknown; 1 manuscript part (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 11, Folder 360)
      Manuscript in Kay Swift's hand in pencil, annotations in red ink.
      Includes chord symbols.
      For bass guitar.
    - [Exit finale], Unknown; 1 manuscript piano score (2 p.); 33 cm. (Box 11, Folder 360)
      Copyist's manuscript in ink, annotations in red pencil.
    - [The sorrows] The sorrows / words by Josephine Preston Peabody., Unknown; 1 manuscript vocal score (2 p.); 34 cm. (Box 11, Folder 360)
      At top of page 1: [Louise Homer (erased)] To Lulu.
      Possibly an early song by Kay Swift.
    - [Unidentified composition], Unknown; 1 manuscript piano score (4 p); 28 cm. (Box 11, Folder 360)
- Scripts, Outlines, Proposals, Notes, and Lyrics, Series II; 1.25' (3 boxes)
  This series includes holograph and typed scripts, outlines, proposals, notes, and lyrics for theater, song, and unidentified projects. Many of these projects were never realized, and a few did not involve Kay Swift. Projects are arranged alphabetically by title, and in each case single lyrics and miscellaneous notes come at the end of a project heading. A full script of One Little Girl (13/409), obtained directly from the Camp Fire Girls Association, has been added to the original donation of the papers. The series ends with 155 unidentified or miscellaneous lyrics. Project files corresponding to some of the realized projects may be found in Series IV. Severely aged or damaged pages have been copied onto acid-free paper.
  - ALL ABOUT ELSIE
    - Script., 30 p.; 34 cm. (Box 12, Folder 361)
      2 copies.
      Typescript.
    - Lyrics., 47 leaves; various sizes. (Box 12, Folder 362)
      Typescript and holograph in pencil.
    - Lyrics., 7 leaves; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 363)
    - Miscellaneous notes., 7 p.; various sizes. (Box 12, Folder 364)
      Typescript and manuscript in Kay Swift's hand in pencil.
  - ALMA MATER
    - Outline., 2 p.; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 365)
    - Miscellaneous notes., 4 p.; various sizes. (Box 12, Folder 365)
  - AUDITION MATERIAL
    - Monologues., 5 p.; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 366)
      Found in folder marked: Audition material used by H.G. [Hunter Galloway] in 1938-1939?
  - BEAT THE DEVIL
    - Notes., 1 p.; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 367)
  - THE BOBBY CLARK STORY / By Robert Lewis Taylor; Music and lyrics by Kay Swift
    - Outline, 24 p. in various pagings; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 368)
      With: note (1 p.)
    - Script., 93 p. in various pagings; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 369)
      Outline only for Act II.
    - Hark, hark, the Clark., 69 p. in various pagings; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 369)
      Script, incomplete.
    - Script., 76 p. in various pagings; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 370)
      With: p. 1-7-8. Unidentified scene (2 p., 2 copies)
    - Choir practice., 4 p.; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 371)
      Script.
    - The horse trader., 3 p.; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 371)
    - The school play., 7 p.; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 371)
    - Well met, as they say., 5 p.; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 371)
    - What makes them laugh?, 8 p.; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 371)
    - What makes them laugh?, 2 p.; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 371)
    - Outline., 14 p. in various pagings; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 372)
      Found in folder with sketches for Hark, Hark, the Clark.
  - CABARET FOR CELESTE HOLM
    - Sketches., 103 leaves; various sizes. (Box 12, Folder 373)
  - CALLIOPE
    - Outline., 5 p.; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 374)
      Based on a novel by Rumer Godden
  - A CANDLE FOR ST. JUDE
    - Outline., [29] p.; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 375)
    - Outline., 2 p. + 2nd page 1; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 375)
    - Outline., 14 p. + 2nd p. 13; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 375)
    - Script., [31] p.; 28 cm. (Box 12, Folder 375)